'Thanks to all Magazines, Television,
Websites, FM Radio and all media people'
Hi! Hello! Welcome back to our show!
Your favourite tunes.
With yours truly, Kathir.
We closed yesterday's show
with a very important question.
"Who is known as the
Indian Michael Jackson?"
Are you eager to know who is the
contestant who got the right answer?
What's up dude?
What's the deal?
Came through?
Flopped?
Bro!
Amazing news.
Aren't we also on the same boat?
Right?
If you try to venture out alone,
Huh?
(Laughs mockingly)
(Popular Tamil song 'Apdi Podu' playing)
Sathish?
Sathish?!
Hey!
Sathish?!!!
(Groans in pain)
Greetings everyone!
We all are there for you
and to help you with problems
related to your mental well-being.
That's why all this
has been arranged
And this "World Mental Health Day"
is to remind you of it
You need to examine
and ask yourselves,
"Why the desire to
get into public service?"
When you introspect,
you will gain an understanding
of the society around you.
The position you are going to
acquire, is not one of authority
but one of great responsibility.
When faced with this responsibility,
you will understand social
equilibrium and its implications.
When you do,
you may experience an
unfathomable feeling of fear.
That fear can deeply impact you.
That fear can push you
into doing many things,
It can also prevent you
from doing some things.
All you need to do in that moment is,
gather all your courage and
face your fear without
a second thought.
Sir is not an easy person
to meet with,
we've brought him here
with great difficulty.
So please ask whatever
questions you may have.
(Chuckles) Nothing like that sir!
You can approach me anytime.
Thank you sir.
Manoj!
Ask whatever is on your mind.
Get up!
Hi Sir,
you are a big inspiration for me.
Since we discussed about
fear a lot today,
I have this question.
Once you became a police officer,
have you ever been afraid of
something or someone?
Could you share about
any such experience sir?
Of course!
'Introducing
Ajay Karthi'
'K. Bhagyaraj'
'Natarajan Subramaniam'
'Introducing
Anjana Murugan'
(Singing a popular Tamil song)
Sir?
Sir?!
Sir!!!
Someone please help!
Here.. there are two..
Why are there so many
police officers near that house?
It seems someone else was
killed in that house.
At this point, we don't know
how many people were killed
Hey!
Scram!
Good morning, sir!
The body has been removed right,
why is there a crowd here?
Sir... actually no, we are
still waiting for the ambulance.
Over the phone, you said
the ambulance was here
No sir, it is on the way
- When will it get here?
- Any moment now, sir
Disperse this crowd first
Ravi, please get these
people out of here
Sir
How are you man?
Super, everything going good
Is everything wrapped up here?
As if, we are still waiting
for the ambulance.
We'll be done in 30 minutes.
He was such a gentleman,
the whole town talks about
how this house is cursed.
Used to wonder why,
but now this has happened.
Whenever I ran into him,
I used to tell him
"Get a ritualistic cleaning
done for the house."
But this happened before
he could get to that.
The boy also died right?
Alright, forget that!
Move my transfer order first,
it's very difficult here.
Chithra has been complaining
ever since we shifted to the city.
Please see to it!
Things are not how
they used to be,
I'm trying to get it through.
Even the top brass is being strict.
That aside,
Why don't you come home
with Chithra sometime?
First you handle this,
- then I'll come over with my whole family
- Okay.
Shall I get back to my work now?
- Alright! I'll see you!
- Alright! Okay.
Move them away!
Get these people out of here first!
Move, move out!
Sir, what exactly happened?
Did you get photographs of all this?
Yes, taken sir.
Where is the other corpse?
Sir, it's in the other room.
Sir, here...
Sir.
Hand me a pen!
When you take notes, write down
that there were only 5 cigarettes.
Okay sir.
You there!
Will the ambulance get here or not?
Sir... Just... 2 Minutes, Sir...
It's almost here.
Hello,
this is the assistant
commissioner speaking!
When was the call placed
for an ambulance?
Oh, alright, will call back!
Full of lies?
Just leave!
I said, leave!
(Sudden gasp)
Balachander!
Get out of here!
'DARK'
Sir?
The doctor is here.
Sorry doctor.
The older gentleman
suffered a heart attack.
Time of death is
approximately 8 hours ago.
The young man is unconscious,
I'll let you know once
he gains consciousness.
What are the chances
of his survival madam?
Unlikely.
We'll try our best.
(Sobs uncontrollably)
He's been disturbed for
quite some time sir.
I tried asking him many times.
He always avoided my questions
saying it's work-related stress.
He's a really nice guy, sir.
He doesn't know anyone here,
except me.
Has he ever spoken about me?
Sir?
Has he ever mentioned
the name 'Balachander'?
No sir.
If you ever recall something like that,
let me know.
Hey Balachander,
I hear that corpses are
calling out your name.
You're a bigshot now.
Hey!
Wash your mouth on the way out.
Moron!
Three years ago, there was a
case registered in that house.
Last week, he was found sleeping in
an ATM in Anna nagar 11th main road.
We brought him in for questioning
and he claimed to have blacked out.
Once we checked the surveillance cameras,
we knew he was telling the truth.
Did his mother come yet?
No sir.
Alright.
You may leave.
Okay sir.
Yes, tell me?
No...No...No!
Tomorrow morning is too late,
I need to see her today
and right now.
Tell her it's urgent
I am on my way.
Somehow get an appointment
to see her right away.
Let's go.
He had his first session
just a couple of days back.
Can't believe something like
this happened, it's shocking.
I agreed to see you only
because you said it's urgent.
Tomorrow I have an early morning session,
I need to sleep.
I keep records of all my sessions,
this guy's session is also here.
Have a listen.
It might be a bit strange.
I'm not sure if it's
going to help you.
He looks to be disturbed,
there's a high possibility
he could hurt himself.
But I'm not sure.
Please call me tomorrow
if you need me,
immediately, I'll come there.
- I'll make a move now.
- Thank you.
"My name is Vignesh,
I am from Bangalore.
I don't have a dad,
it's just me and my mom.
Hey, why don't you stay
at your uncle's place?
Mom,
why do you keep asking
the same question?
I'm telling you,
I will have a crazy work schedule.
It won't work.
It's for just 3 months,
I'll rent out a place.
Don't give lame excuses.
You just want your space to smoke,
isn't it?
Yes mom!
I'll whack you!
Mom!
Just kidding!
Santhosh has picked
out a place already.
I just need to pay
the security deposit
and settle in.
Alright!
Hold still!
Also, drop in and
see him when you can.
He'll be expecting you
- Alright?
- Sure Mom.
I will, just for your sake.
Bye, mom.
Yeah right!
As if you will do it!
I don't need you to do anything!
I'll come and find a house myself!
Hang up now!
What a jerk!
Have no idea how I'm friends with him!
Yeah, I'm here.
I'm just walking in.
I said I'm here,
Hang up already!
You can meet Mr.Ganesh tomorrow evening
and start your work.
Okay sir,
Where are you put up now?
Right now, at a hotel sir.
I need to find a place.
Hotel?
I thought you already found a place.
- Ahem, why do you bring it up sir.
- Yeah Right.
We'll handle it, no issues.
(Chuckles) But you didn't handle it,
You didn't.
It's a joke.
We have to laugh.
We'll end with a laugh and
continue with our work sir.
Come let's go.
You don't have to
report to office everyday,
you just need to be here
when the director is here.
You can work from home, it's up to you.
In that case sir, I plan to
go house hunting today.
Shall I report in office tomorrow
when the director is here?
Do you want me to ask
around for a place to rent?
Oh, don't want to trouble you sir.
If you know of some place,
you please let me know.
Of course,
won't it be better
if it's closer to office?
Sir, he might find it difficult
to find a place all by himself,
Shall I go along to assist him?
Let him do it by himself,
you mind your business.
What?
Do you want his company?
Oh no, sir,
I am in this mess because of him.
It's better I handle this myself.
Good choice.
Alright sir, I will also go work.
Yeah right!
I handle this myself.
Non-vegetarian food is fine,
but strictly no beef.
No smoking.
Do not hammer nails into the wall.
You shouldn't bring girls to the house.
You shouldn't use more than
two buckets of water.
Are you unmarried?
You don't have a girlfriend, right?
Where is your hometown?
Are you working in the film industry?
No!
Don't you work for an IT company?
Do you drink alcohol?
We shouldn't rent the house to bachelors.
You should pay the maintenance
charges separately.
You should use only 2 buckets of water
Are you unmarried?
You don't have a girlfriend, right?
Don't you work for an IT company?
It's so hard to make ends
meet with fuel prices going up.
Better look for other options.
Brother,
brother?
Do you know of any
houses for rent nearby?
Which area?
Somewhere here in Anna Nagar?
Ramesh, why don't you take
sir to the house on 3rd street?
- Sure brother.
- Come, get in, let's go.
The house on the first floor!
This is the house.
I'll go take a look, please wait here.
Sure, I'll wait.
What do you need?
Sir, I saw the 'To-let' board outside
and came to enquire.
Give me a minute.
Here, go take a look
at the house upstairs.
We'll discuss the details later.
Sir,
what's the rent like?
You first go upstairs
and take a look,
if you are still interested,
we'll discuss the details later.
Go
(Clears throat)
Sir.
Help yourself.
Thank you, sir.
Go ahead.
How is it?
Super sir.
It's very nice.
Filter coffee, isn't it?
I'm not talking about the coffee,
I was asking about the house upstairs.
How is it?
Sir!
The house looks classy.
But I am not part of that class.
I don't get you.
Sir.
Let me be candid.
I am looking to stay only for 3 months.
If I tell people this,
they don't even let me in.
That's why I didn't start with this,
I thought of taking a look at the house,
and if I like it,
then we can talk details.
But,
looking at the house,
I don't know if I can afford to stay here.
Thank you for the coffee.
- I'll leave now.
- Just a moment,
Are you okay if the rent is 3000/- Rupees?
Huh?
Is that 3 zeros or 4 zeros sir?
There are only 3 zeros in a thousand.
Just 3000/- Rupees for this house?
Are you wondering why I would rent out
such a large space for just 3000/- Rupees?
Sir!
I can't believe it sir!
Since you were so candid with me,
let me also be transparent.
At first, there were
three tenants upstairs.
For whatever reason,
one of them killed the other two
and immolated himself.
Then after some time,
two new tenants came to stay.
They claimed that
the three previous tenants were not dead
and they are still living in the house.
They vacated on the
same day without notice.
This incident
spread through the town.
The house was then
rumoured to be haunted.
I've been trying
to sell off this house
and move back to my native place.
But, I've had no luck all these years.
Now,
If you're able to stay here for 3 months
without any incident,
I'll be able to sell off the house.
As far as I can tell,
this house
isn't haunted.
Even so,
I didn't want to hide from you
what the neighbours
believe about this house.
I don't need any security deposit.
You can decide, it's up to you.
Forget the three ghosts,
If I can rent this house
for 3000/- Rupees,
I can make my peace
with even thirty ghosts.
I don't believe in the supernatural,
I really like the house.
I can move in tomorrow.
Here's your security deposit.
No need for it now,
you can give it when you move in.
I am already your tenant sir,
here you go.
We'll meet tomorrow.
Hello sir.
Oh, welcome!
- Is that all your belongings?
- Yes sir, that's all.
Alright,
very happy to have you here.
Thank you sir!
Oh by the way,
Do you smoke?
He smokes night and day.
I was just asking!
Also,
Alcohol?
Sir, we are really
conscious of our health.
We strive to have a healthy lifestyle.
Oh!
We'll drink if someone sponsors.
Ah, you and I are the one and same.
Son,
Don't worry, you can call me anytime.
I'm always ready to pour one out.
Alright sir.
We'll take off now.
Yeah mom, he's right here.
The house is really nice.
Yes, really.
Okay, I'll call you tomorrow.
Good night!
Bye mom.
It's fun to drink with friends, right?
Yeah yeah.
Bro!
If I have hard liquor,
I tend to get a bad hangover.
Let me just have some beers.
Sure buddy,
go ahead.
Better you pay in cash.
Now a days liquor shops
don't accept card payments.
You're not gonna buy right?
Right.
I haven't even cleaned my own toilet.
I thought you'd buy me a drink
and scrubbed your toilets clean.
Very nice.
I'll buy my own drinks.
Sounds like a plan!
- Good night!
- Just die!
Don't turn up for my funeral.
And now this...
Excuse me?
Is sir there?
Please wait, I'll call him.
Sir?
Over here!
Son, don't mind this.
We have some electricity issues here.
We'll have frequent, but
short power cuts like this.
Alright!
Do you have a candle or shall I ...
Would you look at that,
the power is back on.
Yes sir.
- Did you have dinner?
- Not yet but I've already ordered.
Why don't you come down
and have dinner here?
No sir, thank you.
Okay then, good night!
Good night sir!
(humming)
I'll need a packet of milk everyday.
Sure, will let the milkman know.
He'll do it.
Alright.
Thanks bro.
Can you hand me the salt please?
This story is a...
Not any love story,
it's a fierce and terrific
love story.
This type of content
has never been seen in Tamil
No no, in Indian
Sir, in global cinema!
Right,
it's never before seen in global cinema.
Have you ever been in love?
No
Once this film hits the theaters,
The younger generation
will all fall in love
Left, right and centre.
And...
I'll condense...
the story and narrate it in just 2 hours.
Okay, just 2 hours.
Hmm
You go on sir.
In the opening scene,
there's a girl that falls
into a drain hole.
Then
from the drain hole, the hero emerges.
The story is a snooze fest.
The poster will be misleading.
How did such a story
get a producer on board?
What's the name of the movie?
One girl
and two guys.
Dude, come on?
I'm serious,
it's a love triangle apparently.
That sounds ridiculous.
I know right!
Whatever.
Let that be,
are we drinking tonight?
I've just moved in,
don't want complaints already.
- You're just making excuses.
- Yep.
I see.
(Phone ringing)
Hi mom!
Yes, I ate.
I'll meet Santhosh tomorrow,
he went home.
Did you take all your pills?
Alright mom.
Okay.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
(Yawns)
(Program on television)
Sir, you're right,
I am the one who borrowed it.
The minute I get some money,
I will repay everything sir.
When are you going to find a buyer,
and when will you repay?
I swear to God,
I will definitely repay the loan.
You say the same thing, every time.
How much longer are you going to fool us
with the same line?
I am not deceiving you.
Alright, when are you
going to sell the house?
I have buyers coming in soon.
- When are you going to sell? When?!
- The buyers will come soon.
No sane person will buy it.
Here, load the programs on this drive.
Your face is very annoying,
can't look at it.
Oh.
So I've decided to work from home.
(Pan clatters)
Not again!
(Panting)
Hey!
(Popular Tamil song 'Apdi Podu' playing)
(Breathing heavily)
(Book thumps)
Hey, you with the annoying face!
You said you're working from home.
You've landed up here the very next day.
Go away!
This is my office too,
I'll go when I want to.
I said, go away!
Moron!
(Sudden gasp)
(Coffee machine whirring)
(Loud gasps)
(Tamil song "Apdi Podu" playing)
(Thumps TV)
Dude, Just listen to me.
Somehow finalise the deal please.
I need to move out of here.
Call me back once you confirm!
Sir...
Son,
I was about to come find you,
I have no words to express my gratitude.
The minute you set foot in this house,
all my woes ended,
you've brought good fortune to me.
A buyer has agreed to buy this house.
All the details are finalised.
Now on...
I'll be able to repay all my debt.
I'll go spend the last years of my life
blissfully in my native town.
You're the sole reason for this!
I can't thank you enough.
My son! Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Why do you look like a deflated balloon?
You don't find my face annoying anymore?
Dude,
there's a lot of power cuts at home.
That's why I'm here.
Flawless logic!
Could have just stayed put here.
Oh by the way, the house you asked for,
I've arranged a viewing tomorrow morning.
No need for it!
Let it be.
One moment you're desperate for a house,
Next moment you're rejecting it.
I said leave it.
Is something wrong?
Nothing like that.
I'm feeling a bit unsettled in the house.
But it's just for three months so
I'll try and put up with it somehow.
Explain to these people and
tell them we're not interested.
(Sighs)
Right, I'll handle it.
- Do you want me to stay back?
- No, I'll be fine.
Don't worry I'll take care.
Okay, let me know once you go home.
Okay bro.
"Darkness is the shade of deathly fear!"
"Only in the moment
the soul departs from here,"
"Will the nights of endless
searching cease to be."
"When the impossible comes to be,"
"the truth masked as a lie,
that I cannot see"
"Won't my eyes find
rest just for a night?"
"Soaked in the richness of blood,"
"Standing on the brink of death,"
"Will those lips resist a smile?"
"That which seemed not to be,"
"Now when the illusions fade,"
"will exist as they're meant to be."
The investigation revealed that Jeeva...
brutally stabbed his roommates,
Sathish and Mohan,
...to death before setting himself
on fire and taking his own life.
The police officers who rushed to the
spot informed the fire department.
The fire department rushed to the
spot and extinguished the fire
Meanwhile, the
Thagarakuppam police conducted
...a detailed investigation
into the incident.
The police confirmed that
he was Venugopal.
The family members were notified.
They arrived at the site of the incident
and broke down seeing
the burnt body of Venugopal.
Venugopal's son has given
a comment on this incident.
He alleges this to be
a premeditated murder.
He says that his father Venugopal had
just wrapped up a
business deal in Puducherry.
He was bringing back
money to Thagarakuppam.
The son claims
Venugopal had asked...
...the family to come pick
him up immediately.
after seeing his father's burnt body.
Further it was reported that the
ambulance did not arrive on time
and hence the son was forced to take his
father's burnt body in his own vehicle.
Police are also looking
at the angle of an ambush
Hey!
Who's there?
Son, what's wrong?
It's just me! I was eating!
Go away!
"My hollow days are shrinking,"
"My haunted nights are long and winding."
"Today, the voices inside my head,"
"Create for me an eternal resting bed."
"Burying my face and
turning me into dust."
"Darkness is the shade of deathly fear!"
"Only in the moment the
soul departs from here,"
"Will the nights of endless
searching cease to be!"
"When the impossible comes to be,"
"the truth masked as a lie,
that I cannot see."
"Won't my eyes find
rest just for a night?"
At 6pm tomorrow,
we've announced the movie poster release.
When will you finalise the design
and when will you send it to me?
Sir,
I've already mailed it to you!
Let's take a look.
How am I supposed to make sense of this?
Shall I take it this way?
That is a terrifying love story?
Where is the girl?
There are three dudes here!
What are you guys doing?
Sir,
we'll come up with a couple
of drafts by tonight.
We'll get it done.
I'll take the responsibility.
Why are you loitering here?
- Tell them I'll be there in 10 mins.
- Okay, sir.
Move a bit towards me.
Get a bit of this light!
And a bit of that!
This is your position.
First take off your sunglasses.
Just cause you were the
cinematographer for "DADA" movie,
Doesn't make you Stephen Spielberg!
Sir, just to check the lighting!
Oh, to make sure I'm visible?
Hey!
Why don't you sit on my head?
That's the comedic angle sir.
Oh there's an angle for comedy?
Yes sir!
You're a genius I say!
Alright sir, at least this
time, let's get the shot right.
Sir!
Yes, give me my lines.
Sir, it's going to take 30 mins
for the shot to be prepped.
You can chill in the caravan.
I can chill the whole day too,
but, one thing.
At 5:55pm sharp,
just like "Thalapathy's" 'BEAST'
I'll be out of here.
I am very prompt with it.
There's a small issue sir,
that's why.
Issue?
Yes sir.
What's the issue?
When asked for a romantic poster,
they've designed a poster
for a horror movie.
Oh my God!
It's more or less the same.
- Where's the director?
- Over there sir.
Let's go see him.
There's some issue with the director,
I'm gonna check it out.
The director is the issue sir.
Hello director,
what's the problem?
Since you're a first time director,
I moved my dates with
"Prabhas" to be here.
Why are you stretching my time?
Sir, they messed up the movie poster.
- Huh, the poster?
- Show him!
Show me!
When asked for a romantic poster,
they've designed a poster
for a horror movie.
(Chuckles)
Isn't he the one who designed this?
How did you know that?
Look at him!
There's your problem.
He's created a poster based on his psyche.
This is a hit for sure!
You get back to directing.
Focus on your scene.
Don't get troubled by this.
Please go.
Brother, all the best!
Be a good man and be a good citizen!
Even the termite repellent.
Yes sir.
Make sure pesticides are sprayed
on all the furniture here.
Okay sir, we'll take care.
Hey Vignesh!
Didn't you hear?
There's office maintenance
work underway now.
They are doing pest-control.
Everyone's assigned to work from home.
Sir, it's alright.
I'll stay here in some corner.
All the corners will be occupied.
You can't be here,
you might inhale some fumes.
Why don't you take it easy for now?
You look exhausted,
rest for a couple of days.
Okay?
When you're drilling the walls,
make sure the holes are not too big,
they'll cause damage.
Okay sir, don't worry we'll be mindful.
Ensure the furniture is all done.
This is the room sir.
Take care!
I'm Vignesh's mother,
the upstairs house is locked.
I tried to reach him,
but I think he's busy at office.
Oh no worries at all,
why don't you come in?
I don't want to be a bother.
Do you have a spare key I can use?
- Yes, let me get it.
- Alright!
Here you go.
Okay.
Do join us for breakfast tomorrow.
Sure, I will.
Look at all the dishes!
(Tamil song playing in the background)
Vicky!
Vignesh!
Are you home?
(Sharp Gasp)
(TV plays)
(Book thumps)
(Gasps)
Mom!
(Heavy panting)
Open! Open!
Come on! Open!
Mom?!
Mom?...
Mom, where are you?
Me? Where are you?
I've been trying to reach you.
Mom, if you're planning to visit me,
let me know first.
- Don't drop in unannounced.
- Why?
Are you up to some mischief?
Nothing like that mom,
I'm just tensed because of work.
Try to understand please.
- I'll call you back later.
- Whatever.
Is everything alright?
Alright, you go to bed
(TV plays)
No, please stay.
I was about to leave.
Are you alright?
I'm okay.
Why do you ask?
My dad would have definitely
spoken ill of me to you.
You're his daughter?
I thought he would have told you.
That I'm solely responsible
for all his troubles.
That's also why he stopped talking to me.
Why are you responsible?
What troubles?
The guy who murdered the others?
He professed his love for me that day.
Once I rejected him,
enraged, he went on to commit those acts.
That's why dad's not able
to sell off the house
and he's breaking his head over it.
Thanks!
What for?
Because of you, he's a bit happy.
You don't have to sacrifice
yourself to please anyone.
That's alright.
Your name?
Priyadharshini.
You're Vignesh,
I know.
You get some sleep,
I'll leave.
"The guy who murdered the others?
He professed his love for me that day.
Once I rejected him..."
"One of them killed the other two
and immolated himself"
(Shudders)
(Screams)
(Dog Growls)
Who prescribed these many
sleeping pills to you?
The only solution to your problem,
is to move out of this house.
Even if you cared half
as much for yourself,
as you do for your house owner,
it will suffice.
Your mental health is also
important, right?
I am not negating all that you're saying.
But everything has a
scientific explanation.
I can guide you only
through that rationale.
What does your sleep cycle look like?
Do you typically stay up late
or
has this started recently?
Mostly,
I work nights.
Ma'am.
I have some
-mental problem right?
- No, not at all.
Whenever you feel overwhelmed,
try to control your thoughts!
I'll give you some exercises to try.
And
try to avoid popping sleeping pills.
Take only the tablets I prescribe.
Feel free to talk to me.
Let's meet next week.
Everything's gonna be fine!
Thank you!
Sir.
- Sir!
- What?
We've reached.
You may leave!
Hey!
Who are you?
Why did you call out my name?
What happened in these
last couple of days?
Tell me!
Hey!
Tell me.
(Screams)
Get out of here Balachandar!
Get out of here!
(Choking sounds)
Here's a ding-dong clock!
Chimes once in the morning,
once at noon and once at midnight.
(Laughs mockingly)
What's your problem?
Problem with me?
You're the one with a problem?
What's my problem?
You're the one with issues?
Let go of my hand.
Do I look like a crazy person?
- Yes!
- Let me go!
Son, get up!
Come on, get up!
What happened?
Oh, no, what happened to him?
Someone give him water!
Come on get up, son
Fear Not!
I am with you!
"Fight back! Fight back!"
"Even if it's an army, Fight back!"
"Collect your troops,"
"go on this man hunt and fight back!"
"Destroy your foes,"
"gather these woes,"
"weave them into a garland of valour."
"Weed out these thorns,"
"fill these tombstones,"
"paint the canvas, crimson."
"Man is meant for strife,"
"history makes it clear,"
"this is a battle for life..."
"War beasts stand up,
fear not and buckle up,"
"march forward looking up."
(SCREAMS)
What?
Hold on!
What's your problem?!
Do I look crazy?
Why are you messing with my head?
If I ever get hold of you,
I'll cut you up into pieces.
You'll be done for!
This is the last straw!
What's your problem?
I've seen enough!
You keep rattling endlessly.
What? What do you want?!
Dropping the books one by one.
Why don't you topple completely?
You piece of work!
Where's the other one?
And you!
What's your problem?!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?!
Why are you putting me
through this torture?!
"Here comes the prophet at twilight!"
"Don't cower and hide from the fight."
"Who is there to save us from peril?"
"Won't the deity now stretch
out to us her arms?"
"Let your sound echo across the land."
"Make a tremendous noise,"
"resounding boom boom!"
"The plight of this life,"
"We have long journeyed."
"In every birth, by your side,"
"as time passes by!"
"The time the savage war sleeps,"
"When the savage war sleeps,"
"Is the time the silent owls
begin their chants!"
Son?
Son, are you inside?
Son...
What is this?
You put up with all this
misery for my sake?
No,
the sale of the house
isn't important that me.
You first move out.
That's not the point sir.
I'm still unsure if all this is real.
I'm afraid I am experiencing
some type of hallucination.
If it's me,
then all this won't change, wherever I go.
Sir,
am I going out of my mind?
When we first met,
I thought you were very brave.
All these years,
I've also stayed in the same building,
I haven't experienced anything like this.
Being a young man,
shouldn't you show more courage?
Alright,
let's do this.
Tonight,
I'll stay here with you.
Okay?
Say okay!
Hello?
What's with you looking
here and there?
Am I not sitting right
in front of you?
Nothing is gonna happen.
Drink up.
Come on, drink!
Sir?
Son! Vignesh!
Son!!
Sir!
Son,
those drinks kept me
firm on my feet,
but a glass of water toppled me over.
Lift me up.
Here you go sir.
Sir, watch your step.
Come, sir
No one turned up?
They will turn up
only if they exist right?
No one will dare turn up when I'm here.
How...
How will they?
Come closer.
Closer.
Was there
any female ghosts?
Tell me.
Sir,
you're cheekier than the ghosts.
Yeah as if they exist
Those three were a
a real handful.
But they used to
tremble at the sight of me.
I see
They had a curfew at 9pm.
If they were late,
I would lock them out.
Once I fall asleep,
whenever they broke curfew,
they had the scale the walls to get in.
They will come only after I go to sleep.
Sir.
(Mumbles in sleep)
Sir, get up.
You promised you'll stay
with me all night long.
How can you fall asleep now?
- I'm done for the day, you carry on.
- Sir, get up!
Go on, go knock yourself out! Enjoy!
Enjoy?
By myself?
Come on.
Don't joke around, sir!
No, I'm feeling sleepy.
Sir, Sir.
Mr. Karunakaran?
Get up Mr. Karunakaran!
What is this?
Did you fall asleep?
Sir?
Please get up.
Sir!
Come on, sir.
Sir, Sir, please get up.
Sir!
Mister?
Get up!
Mister!
GET UP!
They will show up
only after you sleep!
(Growls)
So basically I'm already dead,
but you all are alive?
Is that right?
Good one!
Really nice.
You confused me out of my mind!
You!
Mere ghosts!
I'm alive!
I'm darn sure of it!
(all together) If you truly are alive,
Prove it to us.
(Bottle shatters)
See the blood?
Cause I can bleed!
Let's get rid of this house, sir!
Nurse! Patient has a pulse...
Put him on the ventilator.
Transfer him to ICU.
Vignesh look here!
- Can you hear me?
- Vignesh!
Try to keep your eyes open.
Can you hear us?
- Vignesh! Can you hear?
- Vignesh look here. Open your eyes.
Nurse, continue with the CPR,
don't stop it.
Grab the suction. Connect the monitor.
Vignesh look here. Open your eyes.
Can you hear us?
Vignesh!
Suction the airway!
Keep back the crash cart.
Have you informed the intensivist?
Did you question the gentleman's daughter?
Daughter?! Sir?
Useless!
Get lost!
Scorned Woman Dies By Suicide
Chennai: July 22, 2004
Twenty-one year old Priyadarshini who
was residing in Anna Nagar with her father
Was found dead hanging today morning.
Shocking details emerged in death of trio.
Of the three charred bodies,
it has been uncovered that Mohan
was killed by a stab wound on his neck.
And Satish was killed by blunt
force trauma to the head.
"Forgive me dad,
I have hurt you deeply.
Only after Prabhu became
a tenant in our house,
did I realise what love is.
But I never imagined
he would betray me like this.
To imagine him living a peaceful life
somewhere far away after cheating me
causes me unbearable pain, dad.
I assumed the baby in my
womb was our symbol of love.
But he turned it into
a symbol of betrayal.
I am unable to live
on with this pain, dad."
Balachander!
Who's there?
Did I not tell you to leave?!
Leave from here!
Leave! Leave from here Balachander!
Leave from here Balachander!
I asked Vignesh also to leave
from here but he did not listen.
I wanted to save Vignesh somehow,
but in the process of saving him,
I lost my dad.
"The older gentleman
suffered a heart attack
Time of death is approximately
8 hours ago"
The three tenants upstairs
are to blame for all this.
Eh! Why are you yelling?
Now that we did it, I'm cutting you loose.
What do you want now?
Hey,
he's shown his true colours.
Even eyed the house owner's daughter.
On top of that she's so curvy.
Dude! Don't worry, I'll handle her.
Hey!
What do you mean?
The landlord's daughter, obviously.
(Chuckles)
Bro...
You don't have to stick
yourself into everything.
Why can't we get a taste as well?
The moment I saw her, I made up my mind.
I'm going to be the first one on her.
Watch me charm her first.
Dude, I'm already working on it.
In a single month,
watch me get her in bed.
Bro, pay for the tea.
The way those three looked at me,
reminded me of the utter
betrayal and immense pain,
that Prabhu gave to me.
Their disgusting looks reignited
my extinguished wrath.
Actually....
I kinda like you.
One of them professed his
love but had ill intentions.
If you try to venture out alone,
Because of this, I was the one
who burnt them to death.
I'm warning you again.
Leave this place, Balachander.